[{"answer": "The Alfred Smith Dinner here in just a few moments from now.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "What are we about to see?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "I think at this point in the campaign, Wolf, it's clear to them and it's also pretty clear to us that what we need is some civility, a little bit of humor.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Gloria, why do these candidates normally attend this event sponsored by the Archdiocese of New York?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "I would imagine so.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Don't you agree?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, I think that Ross actually made a very interesting point because if you remember, Barack Obama and John McCain actually used to be friends.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "What do you think is going to happen in the course of the next hour?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think they're being pretty tightlipped about the material that we're going to be hearing later on this evening.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "How is preparing to tell some jokes?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Cadeau?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "You know, one thing I'm reminded of, Wolf, is how important presidential joke writers are.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Is that what it is?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "I thought he was funny.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "What did you think, Gloria?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "I thought he was funny.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Gloria, what did you think?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "I -- I agree with the whole panel.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "How did they do?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Yes, I look forward to wearing those white ties.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Don't you?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I was surprised by that poll, Wolf.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Were you surprised by this poll?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "No, those were the numbers you would expect to see.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Were you surprised by that?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "And you see new ads from the Romney campaign, Tanya, right now stressing the fact that Romney believes there should be exceptions.", "docId": "121018pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "And the question is, will it pay off?", "qSentId": 588}]